http://www.nonstopski.com/website-privacy-policy

+44(0) 1225 632 165
This page relates to our website privacy policy.
If you're looking for our Booking Terms & Conditions, you can find them here.
Website privacy policy
What is this Privacy Policy for?
We are committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Under the Data Protection Act, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We take appropriate security measures to safeguard your data and apply security standards & controls to prevent any unauthorised access to it.
This privacy policy is for this website www.nonstopsnow.com and served by Nonstop Adventure Ltd and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore, the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.
The Website
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies to all UK national laws and requirements for user privacy.
INFORMATION YOU GIVE US & WHAT WE DO WITH IT
We do not sell personal information.
You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our website or by corresponding with us by phone, text, website chat, email or social media. The information you give us may include your name, address, email address and phone number. We may also know additional information such as your age if you have chosen to disclose it directly or indirectly.
If you phone us, send us an e-mail message or complete an on-line form, we will use your e-mail/postal address and any information you provide to deal with and respond to your query or comments. Your personal details, email and related data will be deleted 10 years from the last communication we have with you.
In summary, depending on how you engage with us, we may use your information:
to deliver agreed products and services to you;
for internal accounting and regulatory purposes;
for statistical analysis to assess our business performance and to improve our products and services;
to keep you informed about our products and services you might be interested in;
to send you an occasional email or newsletter
Please note: we will only place you onto our emailing list for receiving our emails or other services if you have opted in.  We may therefore send you an occasional email to ask if you wish to opt in to such information. If you do opt in you need to do so again after a period of 10 years or your data will be deleted and you can opt out of any email contact at any time by unsubscribing-details on how to do this will be in any email we send you.
LEGAL BASES
Our legal bases for processing your personal information are:
consent you have given
processing necessary for the performance of a contract with you or to take steps to enter into a contract
legitimate business interests
fulfilling our legal obligations.
WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to us; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. All personal information is stored on our electronic database and password protect. Limited employees have access to the database.
We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold. All the data collected by us is stored using reputable software service providers.
PERSONAL DATA AND YOUR RIGHTS
You have a number of rights surrounding your information that we hold. These rights include access to your data, having inaccuracies corrected, having information erased, objecting to direct marketing, restricting the processing of your information (including automated decision-making) and data portability.
We want you to remain in control of your personal data. If, at any time, you want to update or amend your personal data or marketing preferences please contact us in one of the following ways:
Email us: info@nonstopsnow.com
Call us: 01225 632165
Write to us: Office 172, 3 Edgar Buildings, George Street, Bath, BA1 2FJ
CONTRACUAL DATA
To provide your holiday and ensure that it runs smoothly, we (and your travel agent, if you use one) need to use information such as your name and address, special needs, dietary requirements, etc. Please be informed that we must pass it to suppliers of your travel arrangements, including airlines, hotels and transport companies; we may also supply it to security or credit checking companies, and to public authorities such as customs and immigration. When you make this booking, you consent to this information being passed to the relevant people. Information held by your travel agent is subject to that company's own data protection policy.
Use of Cookies
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Cookies are small files saved to the user's computer’s hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but please bear in mind that if you do this, certain personalised features of this website cannot be provided to you.
This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. Google Analytics sets a number of cookies in order to evaluate your use of this website and enable us to carry out actions including (but not limited to):
·       Tracking the number of visitors to this website.
·       Monitoring the number of users on the website at any given time.
·       Analysing popular content on this website.
Google stores the information collected by these cookies on servers in the United States. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. None of the data we collect is personalised and as such an individual person can not be identified by the data that the collect. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information http://www.google.com/privacy.html
Other cookies may be stored to your computer’s hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.
External Links
Although this website only looks to include quality, safe and relevant external links, users are advised adopt a policy of caution before clicking any external web links mentioned throughout this website.
The owners of this website cannot guarantee or verify the contents of any externally linked website despite their best efforts. Users should therefore note they click on external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
Adverts and Sponsored Links
This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, to whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve.
Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertiser’s website through a referral program which may use cookies and will track the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computer’s hard drive. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned.
Social Media Platforms
Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.
Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. This website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.
This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.
Any likeness or image of you secured or taken on any of our holidays may be used by the Company without charge in all media (whether now existing or in the future invented) for bona fide promotional or marketing purposes, including without limitation promotional materials of any kind, such as brochures, slides, video shows and the internet.
Shortened Links in Social Media
This website and its owners through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages. By default, some social media platforms shorten lengthy urls [web addresses].
Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened urls published on social media platforms by this website and its owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine urls are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. You should check this page regularly to see our most up to date policy. We will tell you about any changes to this Privacy policy by showing the date of the changes in the ‘Last updated’ section below. By using the website after the date we make any changes, you are agreeing to the changes.
Resources & Further Information
Data Protection Act 1998
Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003
Twitter Privacy Policy
Facebook Privacy Policy
Google Privacy Policy
Linkedin Privacy Policy
September 2016
?
You’re bound to have questions, so either give us a call on +44(0)1225 632 165 or send us a message below
Stay connected with our courses, offers, stories and more
Submit
Thank you for your question
We hope to be in touch shortly or you could always give us a call on +44(0)1225 632 165
Call Me Back
Call back time...
We look forward to speaking with you.
